appreciate all the pastors that are here
Pastor Ken Patrick Pastor Eugene Mori
with your wife Pastor Rashid with your
wife Pastor the wife to Pastor
kenju uh pastor kagua with your wife
Pastor Prof Pastor William Pastor Anita
and also I've seen Pastor tamani Israel
God bless you we bless the Lord for you
I also want to acknowledge the presence
of my wife we bless God for her may God
bless
you thank you for joining us
today I want to appreciate the big and a
very growing congregation the online
Church watching globally we bless the
Lord also want to appreciate the Lord
that today is the day when our program
airs on
citizen my phone my phone is still on
fire we bless God for the opportunity to
preach through the media
hallelujah amen and so for so long I've
been
wrestling since last year I I tried
to every time I wanted to come and talk
about giving there was
interception and I didn't know why until
on
Sunday not on Sunday but beginning from
Thursday last
week all the way to Sunday the Holy
Spirit began to communicate to
me and and one of the things that came
out very
clearly is that
giving is not an
activity but giving is a
revelation so all the time is like the
Holy Spirit Was preparing me to
understand that this is beyond a
teaching this is a
revelation and as I was trying to
understand
I met a friend of
mine and they were having a very major
church
project and he told me my spiritual
mother all she
does is to declare there is a project on
a
Sunday and declare this is the leader of
that project and immediately after that
the announcements come to an end and
people gather to support whatever is
there and the Lord began the Lord led me
to study that woman of God because a
very close friend of mine attends that
church and
U one day we were sitting with him and
he told me we have a project we are
building a parking worth 750 million and
the man told me my wife and I have
purposed to give 50
million I I
wondered and that was a casual
conversation of course it's a lot of
money but I was asking myself there was
no
fundraiser there was nothing of that
magnitude but there was a compelling in
fact people in that Ministry always wait
for projects and if there's no project
they feel feel bad because they want to
give then I study the history of the
church and I
discovered
that when a sound is
passed what you do men
gather so the First Assembly whatever
people may call a church or a
congregation is a gathering of men
now those men I love what Pastor Eugene
one told me people can support the
project of the pastor but they don't
have the heart of the
pastor so it is easy to have and that
face is what we call the face of
members because members can come and
genuinely they see there is something
that ought to be done and they come and
support what is being done but they
never connected to the heart of the
man so I began to go through scriptures
I studied that the woman of God on this
other side no gimmicks on giving no
emphasis no seed nothing they're just
preaching the
gospel but anytime there is a need men
arising then as I began to study I
discovered the first people people that
come to a man are
members that's the first level and when
they come as
members it is easy out of religious
discipline because people are coming
from different areas people have been
taught the first time we began our
Sunday service a man came and brought me
a tithe first Sunday and he said this is
my tithe and I knew I'm not the one who
taught him so someone must have taught
him that the tithe belongs to the house
of God and members are very
good as Moses was walking with the
children of
Israel they they supported the work of
God and we'll come to that but members
are very good they can support you but I
discovered if all you have is members
you can never do the work of God because
the work of God is done by sons
the Bible says in the book of
Kings it was the sons of the
Prophet who realized the place they were
in was not
enough and when they realized they took
initiative and they went and began to
cut the wood to create room because they
were not members they
never can can I love you today please
tell your neighbor don't be offended
Pastor is just preaching you see it was
not the initiative of Elisha I believe
it was the initiative of the
sons to take responsibility over the
matter because a member attends service
but a son is a part of the
family so so so
um today
today father I pray for
Grace now now and and what happens is
good you know we we we participate but
it is son Sons look at the matter and
they realize that we must fix the matter
now what happens members attend but they
must interact with the mantle of the
grace
carer there is always a
demand before men submit their giving
they first of all want to encounter your
grace and your
mantle the Bible speaks about one of the
women that gave in the ministry of Jesus
her name is Mary
Magdalene Mary
Magdalene history puts us as a woman of
high
trade there is a time she gave to
appoint the apostles
complaint I don't know if you've ever
given until Apostles are complain
complaining and the Bible says
that she went and took an alabaster jar
with oil that was the price of one year
salary before the crucifiction of Jesus
and poured it on the feet of
Jesus and the aroma filled the
atmosphere and the disciples looked at
it and they said what a waste
there is a real of serving God until
it's called
waste they looked at it and they said
what a
waste but nobody understood what Jesus
had done to that
woman scripture declares that out of her
seven demons were cast out how they
counted the demons I don't know but the
Bible says
so meaning that that woman encountered
the anointing of the Messiah and after
encountering that anointing supporting
the ministry was not a problem so the
Holy Ghost began to tell me people are
pushing men that have not encountered
their anointing to support their
project am I speak to anyone it is going
to be
burdensome if out of this altar a door
has never opened it is going to be
burdensome if out of this altar certain
spiritual possibilities have never
happened even though you organize a
fundraiser members will still
struggle it is when men encounter the
anointing of the grace carrier that they
begin now to submit with their substance
to that man
am I speaking to
anyone that's why Mary Magdalene could
not withhold one year salary and point
at the feet of Jesus Judas was looking
at that money and he said this money
would have been used to help the poor
not because he loved the poor that's
what John tells us not because he loved
the poor but because he used to use part
of the offering to help himself and uh
my God I don't want to go in that
direction I discovered in every Ministry
there are
Auditors every Ministry that has Mary
Magdalene Ministry there must be a Judas
Ministry but you can never understand
the sacrifice of Mary Magdalene if you
don't understand her encounters with
Jesus so what is it so the pattern here
is allow men to encounter Jesus and men
will never struggle to serve
him when you give men projects it
becomes burdensome when you give them
Jesus and they encounter him and
genuinely know this can only be the Lord
they will never
struggle I I've been in a school of the
spirit even me I was learning so so so
the Lord now tells me so I meet a man
from that church and he tells me one day
the woman of God came on the altar the
man and his wife used to sleep in their
they had a small Pharmacy shop they used
to sleep in that Pharmacy shop and the
woman of God came and said Lord if you
call me home today what will your
children
say and she said I stand under open
Heaven run and ask God for
anything and the man held the hand of of
his wife they ran to the Altar and he
was believing God for a mega tender he
was an engineer for building a dam in
this nation they went and laid it on the
altar they didn't have networks no
connection but the heaven was
opened and in that meeting they got a
tender wor 2.4 billion from sleeping in
a kiosk to a tender and they made more
than 300 million the man told me the
rest is history how will you struggle to
support that vision
so the burden came on my
side I began to tell the Lord Lord now
this is
you you have to do something in these
days for your
children because there is no way they
can ever serve you with their
substance unless they see Moses deal
with
Pharaoh Moses must enter Egypt Dethrone
pharaoh and tell the children go and
collect
gold and the Bible says they got favor
with the Egyptians so they collected
gold and then in the wilderness Pharaoh
asked for an
offering if these people never collected
gold in Egypt if Pharaoh was not
defeated in Egypt they will struggle to
give an offering in the
wilderness one day I was praying for the
church and the Lord told me the people
are willing to give they even some of
them always say if today I get 130
million I I will take to Pastor make his
announcements land so I asked the Lord
what's the problem he said pray that
there are things may begin to align
because the problem is not them the
heart the problem is there is no access
so you know I pray for you I pray for
your businesses because if we don't deal
with Pharaoh how can we collect an
offering in the wilderness yet Pharaoh
is oppressing men they are slaves in
Egypt yet they are supposed to be
worshippers and there can never be
worship without
sacrifice so there must be a spiritual
power that deals with the powers that
frustr great men so that when it comes
to men submitting it becomes easy but as
I was still in this
school I be the the the the the lectures
shifted and
then the Holy Spirit began to tell me
now listen
son many of my sons have never
known 80% of their life they are
perpetually receiving
they are agents of
reception and it is only a small
percentage around 10 that have
introduced a principle where I use a law
called The Law of reciprocity but almost
80 to 90% they are agents of
reception
okay so when God looks at man I don't
know I don't know if it's my mic or is
the monitors we have good monitors work
on
something make me sound like an
evangelist I feel like you've muzzled
me I want sound open the speakers you're
doing a good job I know when you're
there you hearing well come and hear it
from here so that you know so that you
know what to adjust amen because um I I
need this sound thank you now
listen what what has
happened when it comes to matters
giving we
have introduced
covetousness greed and lust and we've
introduced the spirit of
trade those four things are very
important when it comes to giving we
have introduced number one
covetousness Co viciousness there are
four things that we have introduced and
that's why our giving does not make
sense number one we have introduced
covetousness what is
covetousness many people when they share
their
testimonies what happens people begin to
cver what they have and in the process
of cting what they have we sometimes
adopt their pattern and think it is
going to work for us
a good example a man will come and say
like I remember we were in the men
meeting and one of the men Mr kagiri
came and said this time I challenged
myself and I said I want to give
something I've never
given and he said to my surprise within
two weeks the Lord had already supplied
what I had intended to give and even
more now that's a genuine testimony it
came from a genuine conviction but you
might decide to apply his pattern and it
will not work for you so what is making
you desire his results is
greed so you have converted what he has
and now you want to apply his method and
think you will get his results am I
speaking to anyone so the first thing
that has happened some of the
testimonies are
genuine but the interaction of that man
with God is what we don't know the Lord
can tell me give out your
house and the next thing 5 years later I
come and tell you I gave out my house
and this and this has happened and now
someone out of covetousness goes and
gives out his house and he will not get
the results I got because my
instructions were
different have you ever realized the
Lord has never asked for another Isaac
the patterns of Abraham were not the
patterns of
David do you know the Bible says that
David gave for the temple he provided
everything even contracts with Nations
that Lebanon will supply the wood the
contract is sealed the day you need wood
go to Lebanon he supplied the gold and
everything he supplied the the the
historians say he gave more than a
billion for the work of God and after
that giving he repented he said Lord Who
Am my to give to you yet all that I have
is yours it is called when a custodian
of his treasur gives to the
owner the language is custody not
ownership he just knew I'm handling
God's
things just ask your neighbor if you
give a
billion will you demand to sit next to
Pastor on
Sunday H sponsors of Life
Church the man
gave the the project Temple was a onean
project called Danel David
he gave to a point Israel became ashamed
and joined
him when he went to meet God in the
altar he said Lord Who Am I who am I
that I should give to you yet all that I
have is
yours it's the mindset of a custodian
but we have many people that carry the
mindset of
ownership one Lory of balance
they want to audit the
project I came with love tell your
neighbor
neighbor now now so the second thing we
have also introduced is
greed number one is covetousness some
testimonies are genuine but in it you
begin to sense that there is people are
converting blessings please when a man
is lifted bless the
lifter when a man says I gave a million
and God open doors lift your hands and
say Lord we give you glory you're the
lifter of
men my way may not be your way the
second thing is that we have activated
greed
greed there is a lot of material
blessing
conversation and this greed is what has
in roduce the point number Point number
three which is
trade and I'm going to talk about them
does God blessed materially
yes is the blessing of God only material
no Pastor is a house a blessing
maybe is a car blessing
maybe it depends with how you view it
and because
of this greed
prosperity and God prospers men but I
discovered it is dead men that can
handle the prosperity of a living
God as long as you are alive to
self some things may not be handled
because there is no capacity it's not
that God doesn't want you to handle but
there is no capacity to handle them so
there is a lot of greed and greed has
introduced
trade giving has been made as a pyramid
scheme
whereby you give 10,000 God will give
you a 100,000 you give a 100,000 God
will give you a million it's a
lie Pastor are you against sewing no I'm
not against sewing I know I saw a video
going around and I'll tell you where all
these things of sewing came from
when you have prophetic Sons and
Daughters there is a nature in them that
understands how to reciprocate
prophetically
Saul is looking for the Lost donkeys of
his
father Saul is there looking for the
donkeys and he can't get
them and then he has a servant and they
hear there is a
sear a man that carries spirit ual
intelligence over matters and they are
disturbed because they ask each other
how can we go to look for a sear without
a
gift so they understand there are
certain prophetic patterns whereby you
don't look for a prophet
empty-handed but again a prophet is not
motivated by your gift to
prophesy are you getting the pattern so
it is not the gift that makes the man
prophesy
but there is a pattern that you you
can't meet a prophet empty-handed so
Saul understands and they have to look
for a gift but Samuel is not motivated
by the gift he actually feeds
them he tells them go to the upper room
there is meat and then prophesies to
Saul because it is not the gift that
provokes the
prophecy but now we've made it look like
it is the gift that will provoke the
prophecy now we have entered greed and
trade that I need a seed for God to
speak but God is not motivated by
seed the second thing about seed came
with the apostolic
movement the Apostolic movement was very
genuine
because most of the times when the the
movement began many apostles did not
have what they call resident
churches they were what they what they
call nowadays itinary Ministry like I'm
moving to D in Life church tomorrow I'm
in redeemed the other day I'm in nakuru
and so nobody knew about my operation so
when I come to Life Church people began
to be creative and they will come with
an envelope on Monday so I'm doing seven
days Revival meeting and on Monday I'll
come with an envelope and I'll come and
tell the people if you need to support
my Ministry then get this envelope on
Monday pray about it and then you can
deliver the envelope the day you want
and many apostles were genuine they went
to the body of Christ and they preached
but again that Ministry was hijacked
that now an apostle will come with his
envelope
carers so invited in Life Church and I
have my four men and on day one my first
responsibility is to hand over an
envelope to every man there is a man of
God who came to our church in narok and
he said I am going to a certain town I
am not sure what I will eat or even what
I will wear and you can bless me you can
buy me a suit you can you can buy me a
shoe you can bless me because in I I
don't put a price tag to my preaching I
preach to the body of Christ and that
was the genuine Spirit of the apostolic
that I am not going to a church because
of the weight of the envelope I am going
to a church because these are the sons
of
God there's a place we went with my wife
the man of God brought us an envelope we
were newly married and he said we want
to bless you and then he said you know
even today we don't know what the
children will eat in the camp before the
man came the Lord had told me don't
accept that envelope because why would
you honor me yet you have a camp and
children cannot
eat we literally
give instead
of somebody say the envelope
Ministry I remember there's a place
where Anita used to serve a man of God
went for lancha his envelopes were
branded apos to so and so
and so the woman of God is coming and
everyone has a different envelope other
than what they use for giving and now
what happened many apostles
Rose many prophets Rose but what was the
motivation the
envelope and and the whole thing about
sewing now became
trade and the motivation because now
you're dealing with saints that have
covetousness
saints that have
greed those Saints are candidate of
trade but Pastor what happens because
there are men who gave and received
listen it's a law it is in giving that
we
receive there are certain things that
will
happen when men give secondly there are
people genuinely that give out of faith
and it is their faith that was answered
are we still there are we still there
so
covetousness
greed what did it introduce
trade and now people no longer see God
from
sovereignity people see God from
business someone came and told me Pastor
what have I not
done I've given
seeds I've tithed what have I not
done I told him the only thing you've
not done is known God and believed in
him because these things you've done
they don't change his
mind and
so man has been created as an agent of
reception and there are five ways that
God supplies to man
five there are five ways that God
supplies to man five ways number
one God supplies to man out of
mercy God supplies to man out of
Mercy number one God supplies to man out
of
Mercy
Mercy John chapter number
5 God supplies to man out of Mercy
in that book in The Book of John chapter
number 5 is the story of a man that
stayed next to The Well of whealing for
more than 38
years 38 years the man was there what
happened the man never made a
prayer the man was not in faith but
Jesus came and healed the man it is so
sad that even when Jesus is healing the
man
he asked the man do you want to be well
the man tells Jesus there is no man to
push me John chapter number
five you can read that story beginning
from verse one all the way to
15 the man is there no faith no prayer
but Mercy
supplies many of the things men handle
in life when you look at them is not our
effort we are victims of Mercy what
happens when God supplies by Mercy
number one he frustrates the efforts of
man when God supplies by Mercy he
frustrates your
effort that never will it ever be
captured that I was in 40 days of prayer
that I gave a seed and this happened no
he frustrates your
effort number two he also also
frustrates the strategy of
man because man can be strategic and
systematic there is a real where a men
receive out of
mercy and when I'm talking about
receiving please understand there are
things that are above
money do you know dialysis is 15,000
possession ICU per night is more than
50,000 you don't have a million in your
account but you've never slept in the
hospital I I slept there two days and
you telling me I don't know a bed is how
much a
bed it's like I'm in a festar
hotel now you you the the the money you
pay for a bed is more expensive you can
even buy another
bed but the Lord out of Mercy has given
you divine
health I don't if you're getting me the
Lord out of Mercy has made sure that
every organ in your body is working
nothing missing nothing lacking you
can't even remember the last day you oh
my God the way you eat you you can't
even remember the last day you had a
stomach
disorder even how you eat you
yourself tell your neighbor Mercy please
tell that neighbor Mercy
there are things that money can never
count there are things that we can never
put value on but when you look at it you
know this is only the mercies of God it
cannot be the works it cannot be my
activity it cannot be my effort it can
only be the mercies of God man is a
creature of
reception and God has made sure that man
receives one of the channels you will
use is Mercy
no effort nothing Mercy simply means
receiving what you don't
deserve if you were to audit your
commitment spiritually there are things
you don't
deserve I remember a young man we used
to pray with doors began to open one day
he came and asked me must we
pray and even when he's asking that
question doors are still
opening and I knew what was happening he
had reached a place where things are
happening and he can't credit prayer
[Music]
I know there is this language of Kip
G but I can tell you the truth some of
us we don't know the GMA but we know
there is a system called
mercy
and
sometimes because it looks like we have
to contend for every blessing do you
know the Bible says when Abraham arrived
at the top of the Mountain the ram was
caught in the thicket the blessing was
arrested not everything you need to
fight for there are things you can
access without a war because the mercy
of God is
available and let me tell you when you
begin to access things through Mercy you
end up loving God even
more you know that we have been
cultured I need an Open Door 40 days in
the mountain I need a breakthrough 70
Days of Thunder I tell you the truth you
can do 2 minutes of mercy and things are
going to work out and I'm not
discrediting prayer no I know there are
there are certain spiritual disciplines
that we need to develop and mature and
grow but there is a system called
Mercy a man is just lying there he has
not made a prayer but Heaven is
concerned about the man you have been
there for for such a long time he's not
in faith he's not in prayer there is no
price he has paid but the Lord comes and
tells him carry your M and go I want to
announce over somebody May Mercy give
you the chance the Bible says there is
no man to put me into the river there is
no man to throw me when the waters are
starred but there is a man that has
Mercy you don't need for wait for the
staring the man will show up and say get
up and walk because the system of Mercy
is
suddenly may the Lord have mercy over
men there are things you thought it is
your problem there are matters you
thought maybe I never prayed enough
there are matters you thought maybe I
need a seed out of this service May
there be a suddenly moment the waters
don't need to be starred Jesus is in the
[Music]
house someone called me and told me
pastor natut
I like
them there's something the Lord told me
as an instruction it is not scripture
it's a personal
instruction I can't teach it as
Doctrine tell your neighbor God is Not M
to you tell your neighbor God is not
waiting for you another effort tell that
neighb in fact Heaven is concerned that
the blind are
healed and you've been there for such a
long time please look at a neighbor tell
that neighbor neighbor it is your time
and your
turn HH if that one looks like a
different one son of ishmaelite look for
a Jew tell that neighbor neighbor I
sense in my spirit it is your time and
your turn because Jesus is in
town somebody say Mercy
there are things you receive in life and
you will wear a t-shirt called manen
God because you can't explain how it
[Music]
came you know people will ask you what
is your secret and you're like it
sound sh but
Mercy Lifted Me Hallelujah Mercy is not
just supplied when men are sinning Mercy
is when God begins to connect with our
afflictions when God is moved by some
matters that you have been there for a
long time it is time for you to advance
you have been in that situation for a
long time
[Music]
the Mery of God speak over your life in
the mighty name of
Jesus that's the first system that the
Lord uses the second one that the Lord
uses to supply do you know why I'm
talking about Supply because you will
discover that you are so blessed
to do the work of God that heaven has
already blessed me the second system of
Supply is when God begins to meet men
when God
supplies according to his riches The
Riches of his treasury the first system
is the system of Mercy the second one is
the riches of his treasury Philippians 4
and verse
16 Philippians 4:6 The Riches of his
Treasury Philippians 4 and verse1
16 maybe you can begin from
verse
10 but everybody read but I rejoice in
the Lord
greatly that now at last you care for me
has flourished again though you surely
did care but you lacked
opportunity not that I speak in regard
to need for I have learned in whatever
State I am to be
content tell your neighbor be
content
Hallelujah there's a difference between
being contented but still
aggressive now that I speak in regard
now let's continue please quickly I know
how to be abased and I know how to
abound everywhere and in all things I
have learned both to be full and to be
hungry both to abound and to suffer need
I can do all things through Christ who
strengthens
me nevertheless you have done well that
you shared in my
distress everybody read now you
Philippians know also that in the
beginning of the Gospel when I departed
from Macedonia no church shared with me
concerning giving and but you only this
this was a church that supported Paul's
Apostolic Ministry
continue for even in thessalonica you
sent Aid once and again for my if you're
sitting next to a person tell that
person Apostles have
necessities the problem is that the
Apostles of our days have translated
their luxuries to be
Necessities anything that is not for the
gospel you should not support it Peter
said we have left all
for the gospel and for Jesus so you
cannot can I
speak
yes you have no business supporting my
luxury at the expense of your
children and I'm not saying you don't
love me
B Village Market
what you have not done at home first or
to yourself don't do it to
[Applause]
me I'm not here
to take advantage of your hard and money
so that you can support my luxury
[Music]
I believe in the philosophies of Paul of
being a Tent Maker so if I'm flying
first class let it be my
money Pastor in the first
class am I speaking to anyone
it cannot be and I'm not saying you
don't love me it's good by the way you
know but I'm trying to say there has
been a certain image especially online
where Apostles and Prophets and
ministers are now parading their luxuous
life and then we we all know where the
man is coming from
[Music]
because some people their main job is
preaching so we know where the money is
coming from you can't tell me you have
five diners in a week in hotels
expensive and then you put there the god
that lifted men is going to lift you
listen you that is not necessity that is
luxury in such K I'm about to say
something radical in such an area you
are permitted not to give an offering
[Applause]
it's better you go and support that man
who sings in the street and put your
giving there for the gospel it's better
you look for that man preaching in the
matato and tell that man keep on
preaching the gospel because my luxury
has nothing to do with the gospel me
going with my wife to South Africa has
nothing to do with the gospel leave my
holy day alone
put your money for the gospel that's
where the blessing
is for even
inica hey
they want to be like Pastor it's
Error sah I need
to because the God I serve is the god
you
serve the spirit I carry is the spirit
you carry so if we are all on this path
I know God will anoint me as a leader
and all those things but at the end of
the day okay let's continue for because
I'm getting mad because we must we must
align some things for the Next
Generation so that they don't think
becoming an apostle is becoming a
model you FL your open screens and go
live in
prayer as I'm cruising in the streets
the Holy Spirit just dropped a word we
know it's not a word you are showing us
your latest car because how the phone
has been positioned we are seeing it's a
Mercedes
GLE as I was praying in the Holy Ghost
and then we see a a watch that can pay
school fees for 10
students and he reminded me it's good to
keep
time
four tell your neighbor let your giving
be for Jesus and for the gospel El and
you have the right to
audit for even in thessalonica you send
eight once and again for my Necessities
in the ministry not that I seek the gift
but I seek the fruit that abounds to
your account meaning that when we
support necessities of the Gospel there
is a fruit that abounds in the
account Paul is trying to tell them
there is something that happens and then
now he opens up a certain Dimension and
this is what happens now I seek indeed I
have all and abound I am full having
received from EP fritas what did you
send the things sent from you a sweet
smelling Aroma they were things in the
hands of Paul but they were an aroma in
heaven so they gave support for high
school mission but in heaven it was not
high school mission it was an
aroma they gave support for a crusade
but it was not a support for crusade in
heaven it was an aroma oh my God
and says an acceptable sacrifice well
pleasing to God may the Lord raise men
that can give for Jesus and for the
kingdom listen pleaseing to God and then
he says now this one opens a dimension
and my God this is the treasury of
Heaven God does not reward with money my
God shall supply all your need according
to his riches in Glory by Christ Jesus
so men were supporting the work of God
but there is a certain Dimension called
the treasury of
Eternity that treasury of Eternity does
not give gold or silver when when a man
interacts with this treasury there are
things that come from there one is
called
favor one is called
favor number two is called
Grace this is how God supplies to
man a man is looking for a job instead
of the Lord giving the man job he gives
him
favor because what favor will do favor
will not give you just the job favor
will even give you
promotion because the day of promotion
they will not look at CV the Bible says
and Joseph and God was with Joseph and
the favor of God was upon Joseph so the
system of his promotion was not hard
work it was a currency called
favor oh my
God that God has just given a man
Grace is Grace is
greas someone shared a
testimony and said pastor you know
there's a Time you call people praying
for projects now the Lord has opened a
project I went for an interview in that
interview um I said what I was doing and
in that interview they gave me a job and
the person
says Street as a
chef almost half a million contract
three months
now I say this is beyond
there is a currency God is telling you
that you can buy without money it is
called Grace it makes things
[Music]
easy is called Grace
so the Lord will use the archives of
Heaven to supply to man I want to
declare from this hour let these two
currencies that work in eternity may
they begin to work over your life from
this hour going on forward I declare
grace and favor these are your
currencies in the spirit where men have
struggled for many days by the reality
of becoming an amary of the Kingdom
people that have supported the gospel
let it be upon you
now and by there I can affirm this
prayer that Paul
made is still a reality in our
day observe men that are committed to
the
gospel and the kingdom and observe their
Enterprise they move with favor and they
move with
ease it's an Asian pattern when a man
ties his business to the things of God
automatically God must bless that
business because he's a channel to his
thing and the way he blesses it is by
his riches in Glory by Christ
Jesus number
three that God supplies to man it is
called the system of redemption
somebody say
redemption somebody say redemption are
you learning something the system
somebody say
redemption so what is this system called
Redemption Redemption positioned you as
a
son and when you are positioned as a
son automatically the father took
advantage John chapter number one from
verse
12 the Bible says them that believe he
gave them the power to be become the
sons of God but as many as receiv
received them to them he gave the right
to become the children of God to those
who believed in his name so the moment
you became a child and also a Son of God
there are certain things that became the
responsibility of God Matthew 6 and
verse 8 they became the responsibility
of God so the system of redemption
becomes a channel that God uses to
supply to man Matthew 6: said therefore
do not be like them for your father
knows the things you have need of before
you ask because God as a good father
must Supply to his
children and there are certain things
that come to your life not because you
prayed for them but is because it is the
responsibility of the father to supply
them my son has never prayed for rent
my daughter has never prayed for
food and the day they see there's no
food they will cry they know it is the
responsibility of Mommy and Daddy to
provide so it is the supply is not in
the prayer
equation Matthew 6 now go to 24
is it
24 Matthew
6 before you go seeky first where is the
seeky
first
yes
yes this
is 33 yeah now go to
25 I want to show you something
therefore who is Jesus talking to
disciples therefore I said to you do not
worry about your
life everybody
read what you will what you will not
about what your
body about your what you'll put on
everybody read
do you know what he's
saying do you know the warri of man is
these things when we went to school we
were told they are called basic things
food shelter
clothing those basic things they are not
your matter when you are a son of God
this is the Father's
assignment is the is the this is Jesus
speaking to the disciples telling them
do not
worry I'm about to say something radical
do you know food clothing and shelter
should not be in the prayer equation
it should be in a an alignment
position that if I be a Son of God these
things should not be my
worry because the father must take
responsibility okay let's that's why I
said we go
slowly
continue
look look at the birs of the I studied P
I discovered in if you want to know how
to
dress check how birds match their
colors there's a time I was watching I
was in
iasha and there are many birs and I saw
a
birri
orange next
orange God is a
designer the birs of the air and oh my
God story they never
saw
noap 8
to5 as in a
store but yet your heavenly father feeds
them and then he's asking are you not
more value than
they imagine if if my children realize
that I have food for dogs and I don't
have food for them I must be a very bad
father that our God has
food for the
birds and they they don't even worship
him they don't preach the gospel They
don't serve him but he has no food for
his
children
continue please quickly which of You by
Waring can add one or more CU to his
sture so why do you worry about clothing
consider the lies of the field how they
grow these are the grass they neither
toil nor spin but they are clothed by
God and yet I said to you that even
Solomon in all his glory was not a raid
like one of them I want to remind you
you're a child of God I want to remind
you you're a child of God there are
things from this Revelation should be
illegal in your life if you are not
fasting sleeping hungry
is not your portion in the mighty name
of
Jesus and you will not announce a fast
because there is no food it is in the
day of Plenty that you ought to
fast the fridge is full and you open and
say I am not eating I need alignment
lift up your hand and say in the name of
Jesus as a child of God I refuse the
error in my day
this is how God supplies by
Redemption so when you wake up in the
morning remind yourself you're the
redeemed of the Lord I am bought by the
blood of Yeshua I am a child of a king I
can never lack scarcity is not my
portion I walk in abidance I am blessed
the doors of my BNS are filled this is
the prayer that I need to
make there are certain levels where God
may not allow you to walk with so much
until you mature to handle abidance
because the Bible says when you get in
the land and eat and are full please
remember me so there are certain levels
God knows you have not matured if you
eat and get full you leave
him he said to them that a man a man
went and cut wood after using part of
the wood to warm himself the remaining
part of the wood he made an idol it is
called the the inability of Believers to
handle
excess so sometimes God will have to
supply money
monly you are not saving but you are not
lacking because the posture of your
heart cannot handle a million in the
bank so the best
thing Sy Daily
Bread until a million cannot be
something you
idolize screenshot
better balance the money I've spent
during the month can pay doy for three
women tell your neighbor neighbor you
are a child of God and because you're a
child of God
Supply is your Divine Redemption
right I pray that out of this house
things like clothing food and shelter
will not be things that we are meeting
to pray
for Pastor what are you saying pastor
economy it takes Revelation for a man to
rise and say I have never seen The
rashers Forsaken neither them begging
nor seeking for bread so from today you
house you'll never hold a padlock that
you have been locked my Supply shall
come on time I cannot be the shame in
the estate that I'm the loudest at 4 and
on the three my do is on a padlock that
cannot be my portion I am a child of a
king
is a woman of God the mentor of of
Anita she used to make prayers and tell
the lord lord it's end month and we are
only two people who live here me and you
and I don't have
rent and
her so if going to prove to the landlord
you cannot pay rent the shame is not
mine When We Were Young during closing
day those who went to the Village School
the parents will love the father because
the father is looking good but the son
is looking bad and Guess Who Bore the
shame it was not the child it was the
father because it was a sign that the
father was not responsible enough to
take care of the child any time a
redeemed son of Destiny is going through
some stuff Heaven faces the sh
and that's why God cannot allow it to
happen by Redemption right you
covered number four we begin to finish
number four the supply system of God
comes by
love that's the scripture I wanted to
read
today God supplies just because of love
love John 3:16 for God so loved the
world that he gave the scripture we read
commonly the supply system to man come
by Love by Love by
love there are many things man is
handling not because of effort but
because of
Love there are many possibilities that
man is handling not because of effort
but because of love so number one we've
said the supply system the first system
is the system of Mercy number two the
system of God's treasury are we together
and what do we have in that we have
favor and Grace and number three
the system of redemption that positions
you as a son and as a son there are
certain things the father is mandated to
do and number four is by love and the
love of God the love of God is it's not
a love that it's not I love you you love
me do you
know God does not look at a witch house
and say you know what by the way you
don't believe in me it will not train in
your house do you know even Satanist are
going to
harvest and there some of them are going
to have a serious Harvest because the
the the agapos dimension of God's love
is not because of what man has
does is because God just loves man and
there are certain levels that come
because of that and number five there is
now how God supplies to Man by what I
call the law of reciprocity
in the law of reciprocity give me five
minutes is where we have what we call
principal
givings principal givings the law of
reciprocity what is this law of
reciprocity it is in giving that we
receive so we realize that there are
four dimensions that man receives
without any
participation are we
together man receives out of Mercy man
receives out of love man receives out of
redemption man receives out
of the treasury of Zion but number four
it is what I call this is where now the
system of the law this is the the law of
reciprocity what is that law of
reciprocity it means now that whatever
man receives is a product of an activity
of man it is the least level of God
Supply but it is the most common level
that man
uses it is the least level that God God
uses to
supply but it is the most known and the
most common level 90% of our needs are
supplied out of love Mercy Redemption
rights and also the treasury of Zion but
only a small portion 10% is supplied out
of this principle
giving and this principle giving they
are the ones we are we teach a lot in
church there are four of them number one
is
tithe number two is first
fruit number three is arms number four
is
vows number one is tithe there are four
of
them this is the system of the law of
reciprocity the system of the law of
reciprocity number one is tithe tithe
and and we know the blessing of tithe
Malachi 3:10 what tithe do to a Believer
two things happen when a man tithes
number one when a man is tithing tithing
is
not every giving in the New Testament is
a giving out of love is not out of law
the second thing tithe according to the
New Order and the New Testament we don't
give tithe out of law we give out of
Revelation and every giving in the new
is giving as a type of worship the first
tithe was not given to God by Abraham as
a demand it was given as a
revelation the man has slaughtered Kings
and he has met the king of Salem the
king does not demand a tithe but the man
gives him a tithe and the King gives him
Bread and Wine meaning that if there is
no revelation we come to the place of
obligation when we introduce obligation
we are now in trade we are doing
business with God
because the moment Revelation is lost
and obligation is introduced and then
there are now certain things like we
giving obligatory it begins now to place
certain unnecessary demands upon Zion
because now it looks like because I have
done Heaven ought to do but the moment
you give out of Revelation it is an
activation of certain
possibilities and one of the things
giving most of the giving is a sign of
trusting in God the second thing tithe
does is that it opens the windows of
Heaven what are the windows of Heaven
this is a language of Supernatural
Supply there are two times when the
windows were opened during the floods of
Noah the windows were opened and the
rains came and filled the Earth the
second time when the windows were open
in the book of Kings the Bible says will
there be Supply in Samaria unless the
windows of Heaven are opened meaning
that the economy of Samaria shifted
within 24 hours because the windows of
Heaven were opened so tithe is an
activator of the windows of
Heaven am I speaking to anyone remember
90% of your supply system is not tied to
the principle giving are we together up
to there that's why a man can refuse to
tithe he will still walk in
abundance but there are certain
dimensions of the principle giving that
that man cannot access because now God
has tied the principle giving with
certain possibilities one of them is to
activate the windows of Heaven the
second thing as you tithe is a system of
security the Bible says I the Lord will
rebuke the devorer so there is divine
security over what man is
assembling that war of rebuking the deor
cannot be done on the altar it is under
the system called
tithing system are we together that
means if it is not and I will rebuke the
devorer for your sake so that he will
not destroy the fruit of your ground nor
shall the vine fail to bear fruit for
for for you in the field says the Lord
of host so the windows of Heaven are
open and there is a
rebuke because the system of tithe is a
system of honoring the Lord as the Lord
number two first fruit a first fruit is
the first harvest that came from the
ground I I saw it in the
spirit sometimes I sleep but my spirit
does not sleep and and what I saw
was for anything to produce it takes
Supernatural
power so what the man was doing when an
animal delivers the first animal that
means that animal has never delivered
anything this is a virgin womb
supernaturally something has entered
incubated matured and it is now
delivered and a man will look at that
which is delivered and take it as a
first harvest take it to the Altar and
tell the Lord thank you for the
supernatural delivery a first fruit is
also considered as a
Thanksgiving because it is the harest
that you have received after you planted
so the Lord has supernaturally supplied
what happens is that Israel was an
agriculture economy so the lord gave
them the land they came from Egypt the
lord gave them Canaan the Lord
covenanted with Abraham that Canaan is
your land so they didn't own the land
the lord gave them the Reigns there was
the former rain and the latter rain and
the lord gave them the seed so whatever
they were doing is to manage the
Harvest that's why when the Lord looks
at Israel from an economy of the land is
mine the seed is mine the rains are mine
and so the Harvest is also mine you just
need to thank me for the Harvest bring a
tithe and the first fruit bring it as a
Thanksgiving now when when when the
system of your supply is effort you'll
struggle with this principle
because the moment you know I am God
made then ideally it means everything
that I'm handling came from him but if
it is my decree my effort my intellect
my my my my system and all these things
we will negotiate anytime there is an
argument on the principal giving begin
to locate the source of that
man if the source is God that man will
never argue if the source is self and
you know yourself you'll begin to feel
like why does God want my money but when
I know this door it Bears the name of
God when I know where I am today in
life he has given me the RS on time
there's nothing I
owe I'll honor him with a tithe for his
lordship
and 10% 10 10 that's a complete giving
10 is the number of divine Perfection so
first fruit is the first harvest and is
a Thanksgiving and it carries a mystery
because later Jesus identified as a
first
fruit later he identified as a first
fruit and some of these things are are
triggers in the spirit because one of
the things when a man gave a first fruit
he was securing the in Harvest so let's
assume you have a garden that has a
th000
apples and you realize among the apple
trees only 100 have matured first so in
the 100 you take the best after taking
the best you now take it in a basket as
the first fruit what you trying to say
one you are connecting the Lord to the
Harvest you are thanking the lord for
the Harvest you are also saying Lord I
know the remaining apples will also
mature you are also also securing the
Harvest and let me say something that
will mess many of you this principal
giving will not take any man to
Heaven you can tithe and perish you can
be faithful in your first fruit and go
to hell that's why it is put under
principle this one you can be a sinner
exercise it you get the blessing that's
the
mystery man went and asked and he
discovered you know when you preach to
Indians they always interrogate you went
and discovered The God Who blesses is
the god of the chrisan
Chans he hired a theologian and told him
study that Bible and tell me all the
secrets that provokes a man to walk in
blessing and the man was taught about
the patterns of giving that Indian used
to
tithe no relationship with God but he
understood this principle once activated
it works number three and you can see
that in the book of you know you look at
the Book of Daniel 26 and: 6 it's about
the first fruit about the first fruit
number three we look at the something
called the arms the
arms I I know let me let me correct this
scripture uh from the pulpit I know now
people are bashing the church and
they're saying when you go to church and
you give whatever the right hand gives
the left should not know that is when
you're giving the
arms when you're giving to the poor what
you are giving should not be
known so if those leaders are giving for
projects I don't know how that should be
handled because
again the projects of God should be
handled by the sons of
God I don't believe a politician should
come and take over the project of Life
church that's the project of the sons in
the
house Hallelujah am yes so he must move
from members to sons and the other level
from Sons you become men of men that's a
very high level
the Bible says there were three men that
were close to the heart of
David and they had the desire of David
he desired the wats of Jerusalem and
they went and broke the Garrison of the
Philistines and fetched the
water that level of becoming a man of a
man it means you are so close to that
man when David became the king there are
men who came and said from today we are
your men we are not Sons we are your men
anytime something happens any time
something happens the first people to
leave are
members the second sometimes he Sons but
men of men will fight with you until the
end that's why David look at these three
men they were three he had 400 in a
douam but only three were close to his
heart to pick Whispers desires and took
it as a command when you have a church
where you have men of men my good
goodness nothing is impossible with that
church the funniest thing they they they
are sons who fight their
father they are members who fight their
father they are leader but men of men
David is seated and he says I desire the
waters he seated he doesn't even say in
his heart he desires the waters the men
wake up risk their life and they say
here is the water David looked at them
and say this is human blood he bored it
he couldn't take it when he's writing
his journals at the end of the chapters
he says and these are the men of
David this is beyond
loyalty this is when men are now under
you with you and in you that they can
pick the
frequencies of your
heartbeat somebody say arms this is what
you give to the poor there was a woman
who resurrected taba because of
arms the people could not allow her to
Die the intervention of Cornelius was
out of arms in the book of Acts chapter
number 10 the man gave to the poor but
he was not born again the Lord came for
his
soul that a whole Apostolic Convoy was
designed for an arm Giver
God is concerned about the
poor and I'll encourage us all of us
please this is something that opens
abundance Proverbs
14:31
arms let me tell you how sometimes I
do I don't
you don't Bain in a
supermarket someone in a Kanda they in
need more than a supermarket I sat down
with a supermarket owner he told me my
profits per year are 50
billion
Supermarket
if can I speak
but we stop our big CS to Bain
things I said it is
error I know he needs the
money personally that's how I always say
at least this one is
working
yes if all of us decided to change the
lifestyle of the house helps that come
to help us
you just decide this is a innocent Soul
she has children she has needs maybe pay
school fees for one of the children we
will be changing
Kenya we will be changing Kenya some of
those women and
men life just happened I know some of
them even wanted to go to school you
just tell them go I'm going to pay
school fees it is more powerful to bless
that person than go to a children's home
during your
birthday that one is to massage your
spiritual
ego am I making sense personally I
decided
and I left that place feeling proud you
don't in a
supermarket tell your neighbor neighbor
the needy are very close to us if only
we open our eyes
and become a blessing look at Proverbs
14:31 and I bless the Lord I know some
of you that's what you do one of my
neighbors Al anytime my hous help is
going for Holiday I must give her
holiday allowance shopping and money for
the
family but but and he's not born again
and he literally educates all the
children of the house he's not born
again we who are born
again oppress us Pharaoh
negotiate what she does and what you pay
her it's not the same do you know God
brought her to your life for a reason
God is testing your walk with that Soul
that's a son of
Abraham so you are here bringing for the
love
basket supporting
strangers yet there is one who Bears the
image of God next to you but you have
never helped that person you can see the
intensity of
hypocrisy some of them come can't even
come with you to
church he who oppresses the poor
reproaches his maker but he who honors
him has Mercy on the
needy look at 1917 Proverbs
1917 anyone that comes to you with a
need is an opportunity for your
blessing he who has pity on the poor
what does he
do please read it loudly what does he
do and what will God
do that's what the Bible
says
message that anytime I help a needy
person God owes
me why many needy people don't see men
they see
God Mercy to the needy is
alone to God and God pays back those
loans in
[Music]
full when I read this
scripture it messed me up because I
discovered those who support the needy
will never lack
can I tell you why rash come this is the
needy in my
town
now you see when I give this
needy what will the needy do he will
praise God now praise
God he will not praise me okay but
because God is praised through me God
will never make me lack so that he can
continue
being
praised how many have given testimonies
of men who helped them but they never
mentioned the man they came and
said God of is God but you see it's a
man that helped you but deep down you
saw God and so God
knows I must make sure I settled that
man may we take care of the need in our
community let it not be written that you
had the privilege sometimes look at what
you
eat chai Javan almost 150
chai that's that money is enough to feed
a
family some of this catching up we do we
spend a lot is enough to pay a school
fees you can decide to fast for one week
you'll be surprised that you can pay
school fees for a whole
time and that's school fees is a major
investment hallelujah hallelujah I pray
that that will be a DNA as Life Church
that the people who come in our way they
will see God in our
lives can I say something else there's
also a level of but gaining unemployment
salaries and all that that I always feel
like it's it's
unnecessary I come from this
belief that anything God has permitted
me to do
is a source of blessing to other people
I know there is the market rate I know
all that and I come from this school of
thought never make a man feel like you
pay them to work for
you let it never look like I have I owe
you because of this money because the
day you fall your money will not pick
you is the person that you feel you feed
that will pick
you always remember that some of the
things we do even now is a seed we are
swing to our children right now God has
given you the privilege to be an
employer and the person you have
employed you might call that person a
hous help one day you will need someone
to employ your son and your daughter
what are the seeds that you planted as
an
employer by the time they are calling
you telling you the work environment is
toxic the Lord will be reminding you
remember the people I brought you away
this is what they reaping don't
frustrate the future for your children
and also even for your own seed as you
take care of that person even where you
employed you are creating a demand in
the spirit that I ought to be taken care
of it's a reciprocity are we together
let's finish the final one God Bless you
that's my offering make sure you put it
in the offering bag you you are not the
needy the final one is called vow
somebody say vows somebody say vows
Psalms 50:4 to1 15 and I'll finish with
this you know beginning of the
year I had a
strategy and I
told I told the leader in
church we are going to Psalms 50 from
verse 14 to
15 Psalms 50 spread for me a banquet of
praise
high God a feast of Camp promises
uh-huh
continue
15 call upon me in the day of trouble I
will deliver you no no no no I got the
wrong one okay I'll get it but it it
talks about I have honored my vows offer
to God Thanksgiving and pay your vows to
the most high God yes yes call upon me
in the day of trouble I will deliver you
and you shall glorify me look at 14 look
at 14
look at 14 everybody
read give me two minutes because this
will help
you before we began the year I sat
down and I looked and I said we have all
these things we need to do when people
are coming today in church I saw them
evading the
mud and I felt like telling them next
year the mud you see you'll see it no
more but we must write our testimonies
is that okay that one day we'll say
there was a day we used to jump here
they were mad but the Lord has done as
well and I'm happy you're part of that
story so I I I I came up and I said we
need to you know ask people to come
pledge and and you know create this
amazing system where people can give an
annual pledge and all
that
then I remember that
whatever people call pledges in the
Bible it's called a
vow it's called a vow when we come to
the language of vows it is two words are
used you honor and pay your vow are we
together you honor and pay your
vow there are many
Believers
[Music]
finances that have been messed up
because of unattended
vows remember we are talking about a
principal giving meaning that there are
certain dimensions of Engagement that
are quite
legal and I have been sensitive not to
put you in a system of a
pledge until you understand what a vow
is
this is my wisdom to you
one never pledge what you can't
deliver never it's better to under
pledge and overd deliver than over
pledge and under
deliver two pledge according to your
grace if you are earning
10,000 please don't write
million in your current status it will
take Supernatural intervention to honor
that million the problem is it remains
as a
vow before
God and so it begins to affect
interactions financially there is a time
I attended a prayer meeting and the
woman of God Rose prophetically and said
I am having a burden over the finances
of the children of God and then she said
the Lord is saying they have not honored
their vows and that's why I am sensitive
you see the way you go to meetings and
then you hear I need 100 people give no
no no please we have tied men on the
altar with vows they can never fulfill
and it begins to affect them because
it's a spiritual principle and it begins
to affect their money
are we to get up to
there you know where I stand I sound
controversial why the the the we need
money for projects so if there is a guy
who should be telling you about pledging
is me but I rather not put you into
a put you in the financial light so so
that you don't
struggle and so there are people who
have made
vows you went to a meeting there was an
anointing you took an envelope said I'm
going to give a 100,000 you've never met
that
vow you went to another one and that's
why I'm sensitive on those things here
because until the Revelation is
understood we might time
in with vows that they never honored now
are you understanding where I'm coming
from so we are not in a hurry we are not
in in a hurry and I reached a place I
told the Lord no matter what project we
are having take preeminence because it
is not in the pledges it is in the
Revelation men can pledge and not honor
they are willing but there are things
that are hindering them but the moment
the Revelation is there some of the
things we don't even need to make
announcements of he will take care of
them so Pastor what do I do when I know
there is a vow that I made and I never
honor the first thing you do is to
repent
about that vow you just tell the Lord
Lord I made this vow and I cannot hon it
forgive me sometimes you look for a
portion and just release it as you
repent and say I made this vow but I
cannot meet it but let this portion
represent my
honor when I read this scripture I
discovered pledges are good but I've
realized my God I don't know oh Jesus
help me I've realized right now in the
system we are operating in many judges
that have used the pledge system is like
the people keep on going down
financially because they are tied and
they don't
know because sometimes it is impossible
for a man to keep his vow to God he has
no capacity because life has Tendencies
of happening so what what will be my
advice my advice will be a genuine heart
and just telling the Lord the day you
bless me I will do your work
am I speaking that Lord I know in my
heart there is a burden to do your work
the day you bless me I will do it when
you have the maturity of pledge you can
pledge but without that maturity avoid
that area these are called principal
giving the man is saying offer to God
Thanksgiving and pay your vows to the
most high these things are paid because
you covenanted you vowed you said I'm
going to give this pledge I'm sensitive
to right I'm sensitive under the
anointing when people begin to say it's
time you can pledge you can s I'm always
sensitive because I know what that means
in the spirit if the demand is not met
and if people are not mature enough to
honor their
vow I know I'm counseling many
meetings but I rather tell you the
truth so asking the Lord Lord so what do
we do we need
resources he say number one pray for my
children that every barrier that has
kept them bound will be broken and they
will begin to have access number two
pray for the revelation of giving
because when a man is a car of that
Revelation they will never struggle to
give number three pray for a heart that
can bear the burden of the things of God
because Revelation without the heart of
a burden people will never do the works
of God and number four pray for sons and
Men of men members can never do
something
things and that's what I want to pray
for number one every barrier to be
broken number two the revelation of
giving to be a part of you that no one
will ever Cass you do you know why I'm
teaching this this is the last time
you'll hear me teach about giving going
forward we are pushing matters of
Revival so this is the last time you'll
hear me talk about giving this is the
last time possibly we will begin to push
things from the altar I am believing God
that that we are entering that time
because I'm going to make a prayer of
faith that whatever God has called us to
do I sat down with a man of God he told
me there is a meeting which is organized
in Nigeria in that meeting the in the
program there's no giving it's taken
care of let people come and serve God if
you want to give the offering baskets
are their gift but it is not an agenda
and it is not an insult of the meeting
they have purpose that we have must
enter some places where worship is not
emphasized men have matured in God that
you don't need a service to give the
Revelation is there the heart is there
the burden is there and I can tell you
the Lord has shown me by a Sign by a
sign and I know at the end of this
service things will
shift yeah we may we will never we will
never do a har here that's the the
spirit of the Indians harambe is an
Indian
God but we will see men that carry the
burden of God we will see men that have
the revelation of sacrifice and above
all possibilities will happen I want to
make a prayer that Egypt must release
your cold stand up on your
feet in the name of Jesus lift up your
hands
in the name of Jesus I announce over
your life every barrier that stands on
your life by the authority of the name
of Yeshua oh my God you said it took
Mary Magdalene to encounter the
anointing of Yeshua for her to submit
and become a kingdom financier I declare
right now let the anointing of the
Living God break every barrier let the
anointing of the Living God break every
yor let the anointing of the Living God
break everything that has hindered your
children from accessing their wealth I
declare favor with the Egyptians from
this hour going forward go and collect
the gold of the Egyptian go and collect
the silver of the Egyptian I decare the
power of pharaoh is defeated over your
life the oppressor sword has no power
over your life from this hour on this
day of the month of March I mark it as a
day in history where the gates of hell
was shaken where the doors of the saints
were open where matter Supply was
settled over the sons of God I open the
doors of business I open the doors of
career I open the doors of your work
people that are jobless I release the
jobs right now in the mighty name of
Jesus people that have been in the
wilderness running around in circles
from this hour from this hour from this
hour let the circle change people that
have been in losses I declare let the
heavens open your businesses are
prospering anything that has stood on
your way I break it I break it I break
it in the name of Jesus I Usher you to
ceilings I Usher you to Dimensions I
Usher you to Heights of possibilities
that you never thought you'll enter
just hold on the
keys I
declare
Lord we have our schedule but you have
your
schedule it's a
revelation and I declare my father you
are raising
Sons Sons that can go cut the wood and
bring it to spand because the place is
small and from this
hour I lay a demand in the quarters of
Eternity concerning your
matters anyone that is identified by
this
Grace because of the Mandate of the
gospel and the works of God and the
assignment ahead I announc your
Enterprise your career your
businesses because of the Mandate of the
Gospel let them take another
tangent Lord we will not be slowed down
we will not be stopped mmon will not be
exalted on this house because of needs
Jesus you'll perpetually be
lifted and now I release the revelation
of giving and I release the heart to
Bear the burdens of the things of God
and I announce from today let Life
Church community and family take a
different tangent on matters Kingdom
Supply and Kingdom support thank you
Holy Spirit for finally allowing me to
speak this message I know this was the
day and this was the time let it be
effected in the hearts and souls of men
in Jesus name we have prayed amen so go
and harvest receive the gold of the
Egyptians and it cannot be
otherwise I am sorry today I have taken
much of your time I was covering for
Sunday so Sunday will keep time
beginning from next
month I don't know how the services are
but um we we are going to take a
different direction and just believe God
for things are you ready to give are you
ready to give get into your pockets
right
now get into your pockets and if you
there and you're not born again just
stand I want to release you I've kept
you enough just stand you've sat for
Longo we have a a meeting in K beginning
from 2 Aza it was there from Friday by
the grace of God we're ministering so I
pray that you'll make it there it's an
amazing time in the presence of God from
12 way to 7 so please if you can please
uh just get there is there anyone here
you want to give your life to Jesus just
lift up your hand I'm going to pray with
you I'm going to pray with you bring the
announcements quickly so that even as
you're preparing to give is there anyone
that you want to give your life to Jesus
first time visitors I know you're there
I'll tell you what you're going to do
please don't walk out please allow me to
collect the offering and then we share
the grace don't live without the grace I
realized um
Destiny kids
VBS
um the VBS team is looking oh thank you
thank you let's celebrate this
brother I can't read any announcement
let's celebrate this
brother is there anyone else there you
are saying I want to give my life to
Jesus anyone else you I want to give my
life to
Jesus my
God this is our year of harvest thank
you thank you thank
you thank you